TOKOYO
a record of observations
OBSERVATION 001
Kurage — Jellyfish
Nothing is drawn. This equation is the creature.
Kurage — Jellyfish — 40,000 points
Kurage — Jellyfish — 625 points
Kurage — Jellyfish — 40 points
Kurage — Jellyfish — 1 point
OBSERVATION 006
Mayu — Cocoon
Nothing is drawn. This equation is the creature.
Mayu — Cocoon — 40,000 points
Mayu — Cocoon — 625 points
Mayu — Cocoon — 40 points
Mayu — Cocoon — 1 point
OBSERVATION 020
Ikazuchi — Lightning
Nothing is drawn. This equation is the creature.
Ikazuchi — Lightning — 40,000 points
Ikazuchi — Lightning — 625 points
Ikazuchi — Lightning — 40 points
Ikazuchi — Lightning — 1 point
OBSERVATION 026
Ei — Ray
Nothing is drawn. This equation is the creature.
Ei — Ray — 40,000 points
Ei — Ray — 625 points
Ei — Ray — 40 points
Ei — Ray — 1 point
A point has no position of its own.
It is fixed only by its relations to the other points.
Take the relations away and the shape goes with them.
chiero.jp/tokoyo/en